pastoral: adj. 田园的
Lesson 41. Illusions of pastoral peace. The quiet life of the country-aws never appealed to me.
第41课。牧师和平的幻想。乡村仇恨的安静生活从未吸引我。
City-born and city-bred. I have always regarded the country as something you look at through a train window.
城市出生和城市繁殖。我一直将这个国家视为您通过火车窗户看的东西。
Or something you occasional visit during the weekend. Most of my friends live in the city.
或您偶尔在周末访问的东西。我的大多数朋友都住在这座城市。
rapture: n.   欣喜
Yet they always go into raptures at the mere mention of the country.
然而，仅仅提到这个国家，他们总是猛地猛地。
extol: v.   赞美，颂扬
Though they extol the virtues of the peaceful life, only one of him has ever gone to live in the
尽管他们赞扬了和平生活的美德，但他中只有一个人去过
illusion: n.   幻想，错觉
country and he was back in town within six months. Even he still lives under the illusion that
乡村，他在六个月内回到城镇。甚至他仍然生活在一个幻想之下
superior: adj. 优越的
country life is somehow superior to town life. He is forever talking about the friendly people.
乡村生活在某种程度上优于城镇生活。他永远谈论友好的人。
The clean atmosphere, the closeness to nature and the gentle pace of living. Nothing can be compared.
干净的氛围，与自然的亲密关系和生活的柔和节奏。没有什么可以比较。
twitter: v.   （鸟）吱吱叫，嘁嘁喳喳叫
He maintains, with the first cockroach, the twittering of birds at dawn, the sight of the rising
他坚持第一个蟑螂，在黎明时twitter着鸟，看到了上升的景象
pastoral: adj. 田园的, glint: v.   闪烁, pasture: n.   牧场, idyllic: adj. 田园诗的
sun glinting on the trees and pastures. This idyllic pastoral scene is only part of the picture.
阳光在树木和牧场上闪烁。这个田园诗般的田园场景只是图片的一部分。
virtually: adv. 几乎，差不多
My friend fails to mention the long and friendless winter evenings in front of the TV, virtually.
我的朋友实际上没有提及电视前面漫长而无朋友的冬天晚上。
The only form of entertainment. He says nothing about the poor selection of goods in the shops.
唯一的娱乐形式。他对商店中商品的选择不佳一无所知。
Or about those unfortunate people who have to travel from the country to the city every day to get.
或关于每天必须从该国到城市旅行的不幸的人。
dubious: adj. 可疑的，怀疑的, privilege: n.   特权
To work, why people are prepared to tolerate a four-hour journey each day for the dubious privilege of.
为了工作，为什么人们准备容忍每天四个小时的旅程，以获得可疑的特权。
misery: n.   苦难
Living in the country is beyond me. They could be saved so much misery and expense if they chose
生活在该国超越了我。如果他们选择的话，他们可能会被挽救太多的痛苦和费用
pastoral: adj. 田园的
to live in the city where they rightly. Belong. If you can do without the few pastoral pleasures of
住在他们正确的城市。属于。如果您可以在没有一些田园乐趣的情况下做
the country, you will find the city can provide you with the best that life can offer.
这个国家，您会发现这座城市可以为您提供生活所能提供的最好的。
You never have to travel miles to see your friends. They invariably line nearby and are always
您永远不必旅行英里即可见到您的朋友。他们总是在附近的线条，总是
acquaintance: n.   熟人
available for an informal chat or an evening's. Entertainment. Some of my acquaintances in the country
可用于非正式聊天或晚上。娱乐。我在该国的一些熟人
treat: n.   难得的乐事，享受
come up to town once or twice a year to visit the theater. As a special treat, for them this is a
每年一次或两次去镇上去剧院。作为特殊享受，对他们来说，这是
major operation which involves considerable planning. As the play draws to its close,
大型操作涉及大量计划。随着戏剧的结束，
dweller: n.   居住者
they wonder whether they will ever catch that last train home. The CIT dweller never experiences
他们想知道他们是否会赶上最后一列火车回家。CIT居民从未经历过
anxieties of this sort. The latest exhibitions. Films. Or plays are only a short bus ride away.
这种焦虑。最新展览。电影。或比赛只有很短的公共汽车。
Shopping. Two. As always a pleasure. The latest exhibitions. Films. Or plays are only a short bus ride
购物。二。一如既往的乐趣。最新展览。电影。或比赛只是一小段公共汽车
away. Shopping. Two. As always a pleasure. There is so much variety that you never have to make
离开。购物。二。一如既往的乐趣。有很多变化，你永远不必做
stagger: v.   摇晃，蹒跚
do with second best country people run wild. When they go shopping in the city and stagger home
与第二最好的乡村人一起奔跑。当他们在城市购物时交错家时
exotic: adj. 导乎寻常的，外来的
loaded with as many of the exotic items as they can carry. Nor is the city without its moments of
装有尽可能多的异国情调的物品。这座城市也不是没有它的时刻
glow: n.   白炽光
beauty. There is something comforting about the warm glow shed by advertisements on cold wet winter
美丽。在寒冷的潮湿冬天，广告散发出温暖的光芒有些安慰
descend: v.   缩进，隐藏
nights. Few things could be more impressive than the piece that descends on deserted city streets at.
夜晚。几乎没有什么比在荒芜的城市街道上降落的东西更令人印象深刻的。
Weekends when the thousands that travel to work every day are tucked away in their homes in the
周末，每天上班的成千上万的人都被藏在他们的家中
dweller: n.   居住者
country. It has always been a mystery to me who city dwellers, who appreciate all these things.
国家。这对我来说一直是一个谜，谁喜欢所有这些事情。
Opsdenitly pretend that they would prefer to live in the country.
OpsDenitity假装他们宁愿住在该国。